so what motivated me to want to become a
business Central consultant is the idea
of working with a large firm such as 4ps
and also Microsoft products as well both
wanting to work hand inand to improve
construction which has been a lifelong
ambition of mine so this Talent program
has actually allowed me to fulfill a
dream which I've had of working in
technology with in construction for a
very long time I don't think it would
have been possible for me to sort of
find companies which specialize in
things that I wanted to do with ease
previously I've looked around but I was
actually lucky that the talent program
contacted me and have supported me right
through from day one to get to where I
want to be I think that to have so much
passion for an industry um you're going
to need to improve it and you want to be
part of that Improvement one thing which
I'm really looking forward to while
working with 4ps is um navigating the
platform I've been on the opposite side
where I've been using similar platforms
I'd like to be on the 4ps side I can
only see positive things in regards to
the talent program
here